I don't get fooled by such talk, see how
good a reel you make, if a fan sees it then
I will catch it, otherwise if someone sees it then
I will be in trouble,
oh bastard, you have made it, aren't
you the one who makes videos, Bhaiya, yes then what will you
say, you will
say that I like you a lot, if you want to woo me then I will woo you, we
make reels, I will woo this one,
why didn't I woo the reel girl,
well leave it brother, I am not lucky, the
reel girl is in my luck, Jhol called,
hello Kari
said, yes ji, hey,
I am going to the bar, yes look,
call near me, tell me that it is time for sowing, make
arrangements for sowing and sow a little from today,
press
[nasal voice] I would have
killed you and the contract, it's no big
deal, I will definitely have to say it to you,
brother, I will tease you, plant
Nirpasa, plant
one second, run away from
here, it's not that big, stop me, take care, put
some clothes,
oh no, you are playing, ah ah bahu
where should you go with your bag hanging, sister
[laughs]
Babuji, I am getting my daughter admitted in Patna,
but what should I do,
Babuji, oh my god, I am
constipated, Bappa,
Babuji, don't do too much, Babuji, it's
okay, daughter, whatever is
okay,
you have a father, son,
old woman, all four are fathers, take care of them
[laughs] I, I'm
not laughing,
but one second the
waist is falling, hey, hey, wait, wait, hey,
Bhaangwa, you stopped there, hey,
break it, some work, okay,
listen, I'll take you, then
where are you, hey,
Bombay, earn money, oh,
Bombay, you're not earning, if you're feeling
well, take it, but
take the fare from your man too,
sister's branded bicycle, you can get the fare, come on, take it, go,
where should I drive it, I'll drive it, you'll have to pay the
fare, friend,
you sit behind, I'll drive, I'll live, I'll
eat from Bombay's hotels, sit here,
hurry up,
okay, Bhaangwa, how much do you get per month,
hey, give me 15000 rupees after eating and drinking
Hey brother,
come on, I haven't changed the village yet, hey,
look, [ __ ] me, I haven't seen any way yet, if we
give the house then the house is a bad place [Music] Get up, get down,
get down, now whatever happens to
our house, yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes sit, okay, hey son, it's okay, I'm going to Delhi, Babuji, I have to do the plantation here, if you get the plantation done then come, talk to me half an hour before,
Babuji,
yes, then leave 20 minutes before, then the
throat is black,
his daughter-in-law is not well, she is
admitted in Patna AIIMS, that means Samiya is
fine, I
hope,
okay, Babuji, I will do one thing, if we can't go there,
then get the work done by farming,
listen, you go and see Samiya and we, the family
members, get the work done here and there, and after planting the saplings,
we will get it done, you old lady, how much yes, yes, I am
saying the right thing,
okay, Babuji, you go and meet Sandhya, get the farm
work done, your Roni is
fine,
sit, okay, Joji,
hey son
Hamsa
[laughs]
oh my god, my father is completely
Aziriya
Moriya Moriya, where will you give me the money for free, hurry up,
Dada,
okay, save yourself from your in-laws' paddy, you should be almost
here,
namaskar Babuji,
namaskar Amma, be happy, daughter, be happy, if you do
n't get any work,
go to the fields, but I will take rest,
stop the money for rest, I will bring food, okay, make an excuse to
your in-laws,
stop it, yes,
okay,
cry, daughter, run away, take a
roti,
hey, Mummy,
take the fare very quickly,
yes, son, take it on rent, yes, that's too
much,
Didi, Didi,
you have sat here, giving a messed up
speech,
how can we treat so many people,
never do a mistake with an
uncle,
this is Dhakanpur village,
okay, okay, see, we, son,
today
everything was fine, we planted paddy, okay, we are humans, peace, hey,
this is my father, do it, give a
speech [laughs]
Daughter, you will
stop us, it is a shame,
everyone has sown paddy, our fate is bad, son, he has
stabbed the canal here, now what should we do
alone,
Samdhi Doot  Samiya is admitted in Patna, Samdhi,
Samdhi, do
one thing, give me a hand, if you are
hungry,
Samdhi, Samdhi,
Samdhi, where are you, I said you, I was
in the hospital, I was admitted
in AIIMS, Patna [laughs], have you
ever seen Patna in my life, so
where do I get the information, daughters, everything,
I haven't had grapes for two years, get me
loaded in Patna,
okay okay okay okay, come and
sit,
old lady, I'm doing a lot of work, it's a lot of
fun, come and eat
Singhada, hey, if
I have four rupees, I have one rupee,
Sarva is alone in the field, he's so
miserly, hey, hey,
Sarva is alone in the field, hey,
call him, you bastard, you have
eyes, you won't
see the potato, you're going, send for father's as well, look at the father-in-law's intentions,
look at the famine, hey,
Sarva, not even for a day, go and see, Sarva's father-in-
law's life, Sarva
says, I don't even see the daughter, I'm
not that worried about father's life  Hey hey you keep taunting your mother all your
life that you did
not die for your father see hey hey why do
I die by killing and eating the food of my father you have to die hey hey I have
not sold you hey she is doing it she is a [ __ ]
she is very hot so it is a lot of fun [laughter]
hey
why are you so innocent you don't go and
see your father at all
if you kill him then your mother keeps taunting you life is
not made by earning money
hey you are right in talking but no
one cries after seeing me how can I live
so far my father in law sir talk about the car I am the
old man I am working okay come on let's go [laughter]
work
[music] I will walk
staring at you in a day look come on sit I will sit sit
quickly
you sit behind
everything like this go on father in law is
not in law's house
everything is fine father in law
eat but
sit and
see a few bulls brother sahib I am
not there sir
pranams sir rah
now pranams brother sahib pranams now
suddenly you also have sons also that means we
daughters are also the second one  What's the
whole story, ask your daughters, the
number one fools, I
mean brother, please explain to me, old man, I want to know everything, that's why I should make fun of
Durga,
sir, both of us, I can take the joke, till then I am
disturbing you,
yes, if you stop, it would have been better, I
stopped immediately,
okay,
sister, let's go, hey sister, you are a number one
bad boy,
when you have studied so much English, then why do you take up a job,
leave everything, sister, have you not seen your brother-in-law's daughter, he is
Dhana, now tell me, tie yourself
to Dhana, daughter,
understand, then this is what I have lost, father-in-law,
yes, this is what I have lost, hey Ratiya, I do
n't know, come on, hey,
where is the family, you hide, leave it
alone in the storm, and try to flirt, hey, I do
n't understand, hey, [ __ ], it's
very cool, hey, brother-in-law, wait, wait, wait,
see, I am Bappa, I am Dhana next to me,
of course you are my father  Beni, don't
look, go and hit him
quickly, go quickly,
hey old man, now I am about to kill you,
hey father, hey
son, leave me, hey
old man, hey, I am running
behind, come on, I am a bastard, hey
friends, how did you like this video,
please tell me in the comments, if you are new to the channel, then please
subscribe to the channel, and also do not forget to
press the bell icon,
share the videos, share them a
little, all of them are small children.   We have
great expectations.  Kari ke
nahi jholai watch Kari Jholai by guys what
else do you
want to say by sharing the video
and yes especially do comment from
where are you watching this video?  Which
village, which district, which city and which
country or state are you from?  And
which part of the video did you like?  Whose character
is good?  In this way, you people
give a lot of love to the character of Bhai Kari.
Feels very good.  Thank you so much.  Just
keep giving your love and blessings like this and do share the videos.